

 const addition = [
    {
        question: " 111 + 112 = ",
        options: ["223", "224", "221", "222"],
        correctAnswer: "223",
        level:"Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 2 + 2 = ",
        options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
        correctAnswer: "4",
        level:"Easy"

    },
    {
        question: " 278 + 674 = ",
        options: ["952", "953", "955", "961"],
        correctAnswer: "952",
        level:"Difficult"

    },
    {
        question: " 16 + 16 = ",
        options: ["32", "34", "35", "33"],
        correctAnswer: "32",
        level:"Easy"

    },
    {
        question: " 100 + 200 = ",
        options: ["300", "299", "298", "301"],
        correctAnswer: "300",
        level:"Medium"

    },
    {
        question: " 310 + 630 = ",
        options: ["940", "942", "941", "943"],
        correctAnswer: "940",
        level:"Difficult"

    },
    {
        question: " 5 + 8 = ",
        options: ["13", "14", "15", "16"],
        correctAnswer: "13",
        level:"Easy"

    },
    {
        question: " 101 + 202 = ",
        options: ["303", "304", "308", "3066"],
        correctAnswer: "303",
        level:"Medium"

    },
    {
        question: " 510 + 1030 = ",
        options: ["1540", "1541", "1542", "1544"],
        correctAnswer: "1540",
        level:"Difficult"

    },
    {
        question: " 9 + 10 = ",
        options: ["19", "20", "18", "22"],
        correctAnswer: "19",
        level:"Easy"

    },
    {
        question: " 200 + 400 = ",
        options: ["600", "601", "602", "605"],
        correctAnswer: "600",
        level:"Medium"

    },
    {
        question: " 1310 + 2030 = ",
        options: ["3340", "3342", "3341", "3343"],
        correctAnswer: "3340",
        level:"Difficult"

    },
    {
        question: " 7 + 8 = ",
        options: ["13", "14", "15", "16"],
        correctAnswer: "15",
        level:"Easy"

    },
    {
        question: " 212 + 121 = ",
        options: ["333", "334", "338", "336"],
        correctAnswer: "333",
        level:"Medium"

    },
    {
        question: " 1212 + 1080 = ",
        options: ["2292", "2291", "2290", "2295"],
        correctAnswer: "2292",
        level:"Difficult"

    },
];


const subtraction = [

    {
        question: " 5 - 3 = ",
        options: ["2", "1", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 10 - 4 = ",
        options: ["6", "5", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 20 - 10 = ",
        options: ["10", "12", "8", "15"],
        correctAnswer: "10",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 30 - 15 = ",
        options: ["15", "10", "20", "25"],
        correctAnswer: "15",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 50 - 25 = ",
        options: ["25", "20", "30", "35"],
        correctAnswer: "25",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    

    {
        question: " 100 - 45 = ",
        options: ["55", "60", "50", "65"],
        correctAnswer: "55",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 200 - 75 = ",
        options: ["125", "130", "120", "115"],
        correctAnswer: "125",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 350 - 150 = ",
        options: ["200", "180", "170", "190"],
        correctAnswer: "200",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 500 - 250 = ",
        options: ["250", "300", "200", "400"],
        correctAnswer: "250",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 600 - 300 = ",
        options: ["300", "250", "350", "400"],
        correctAnswer: "300",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    

    {
        question: " 1000 - 456 = ",
        options: ["544", "546", "550", "558"],
        correctAnswer: "544",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 1500 - 789 = ",
        options: ["711", "721", "701", "731"],
        correctAnswer: "711",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 2500 - 1250 = ",
        options: ["1250", "1500", "1000", "2000"],
        correctAnswer: "1250",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 3000 - 1500 = ",
        options: ["1500", "1600", "1400", "1700"],
        correctAnswer: "1500",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 5000 - 2500 = ",
        options: ["2500", "3000", "2000", "4000"],
        correctAnswer: "2500",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
];

const multiplication = [
    
    {
        question: " 2 × 3 = ",
        options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 4 × 5 = ",
        options: ["20", "18", "22", "24"],
        correctAnswer: "20",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 6 × 7 = ",
        options: ["42", "40", "44", "38"],
        correctAnswer: "42",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 3 × 9 = ",
        options: ["27", "24", "30", "21"],
        correctAnswer: "27",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 5 × 5 = ",
        options: ["25", "20", "30", "15"],
        correctAnswer: "25",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    

    {
        question: " 12 × 8 = ",
        options: ["96", "98", "100", "92"],
        correctAnswer: "96",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 15 × 6 = ",
        options: ["90", "80", "100", "70"],
        correctAnswer: "90",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 9 × 11 = ",
        options: ["99", "88", "100", "90"],
        correctAnswer: "99",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 14 ×  7 = ",
        options: ["98", "96", "94", "92"],
        correctAnswer: "98",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 18 × 5 = ",
        options: ["90", "80", "100", "70"],
        correctAnswer: "90",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    

    {
        question: " 25 × 24 = ",
        options: ["600", "550", "650", "700"],
        correctAnswer: "600",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 30 × 19 = ",
        options: ["570", "580", "590", "600"],
        correctAnswer: "570",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 45 × 12 = ",
        options: ["540", "550", "530", "520"],
        correctAnswer: "540",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 36 × 15 = ?",
        options: ["540", "550", "530", "520"],
        correctAnswer: "540",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 50 × 40 = ",
        options: ["2000", "2100", "2200", "2300"],
        correctAnswer: "2000",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
];


const division = [
 
    {
        question: " 6 ÷ 2 = ",
        options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        correctAnswer: "3",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 10 ÷ 5 = ",
        options: ["2", "3", "1", "5"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 15 ÷ 3 = ",
        options: ["5", "6", "4", "7"],
        correctAnswer: "5",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 8 ÷ 4 = ",
        options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        level: "Easy"
    },
    {
        question: " 12 ÷ 6 = ",
        options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        level: "Easy"
    },


    {
        question: " 36 ÷ 6 = ",
        options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 81 ÷ 9 = ",
        options: ["9", "8", "10", "7"],
        correctAnswer: "9",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 48 ÷ 8 = ",
        options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        correctAnswer: "6",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 64 ÷ 16 = ",
        options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        correctAnswer: "4",
        level: "Medium"
    },
    {
        question: " 100 ÷ 25 = ",
        options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        correctAnswer: "4",
        level: "Medium"
    },


    {
        question: " 144 ÷ 12 = ",
        options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
        correctAnswer: "12",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 225 ÷ 15 = ",
        options: ["14", "15", "16", "17"],
        correctAnswer: "15",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 625 ÷ 25 = ",
        options: ["24", "25", "26", "27"],
        correctAnswer: "25",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 1000 ÷ 50 = ",
        options: ["20", "25", "30", "15"],
        correctAnswer: "20",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
    {
        question: " 360 ÷ 45 = ",
        options: ["8", "7", "9", "10"],
        correctAnswer: "8",
        level: "Difficult"
    },
];

export {addition, subtraction, multiplication, division};

